Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part II WAG.025.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Immigration, Resettlement and Refugee Aid
  - Subseries IV:D: Child Adoption Case Files
    - Adoption Case File Microfilm Reels
      - Peterfant, Pesa to Reichert, Marian, undated (Reel 357)
      - Reisman, Joseph to Salvaneschi, Antonio, undated (Reel 358)
      - Sambol, Jankel to Sonnenblick, Janka, undated (Reel 359)
      - Sonnino, David to Terracina, Cesare, undated (Reel 360)
      - Tesler, Robert to Warszawska, Hania, undated (Reel 361)
      - Wartska, Emilja to Zaksowna, Zofja, undated (Reel 362)
      - Zalchberg, Waclaw to Zysman, Isaac, undated (Reel 363)
  - Subseries IV:E: Displaced Persons Card Files
    (Originals stored in JLC Boxes Add. 14-22; see staff for access.)
    - Immigrantion/Aid Cards A-K (Box 564)
    - Immigrantion/Aid Cards K-S (Box 565)
    - Immigrantion/Aid Cards T-Z (Box 566)
    - Immigration/Aid Microfilm Reel: Abbe, Szmul to Rzezak, Israel, undated (Reel 364)
    - Immigration/Aid Microfilm Reel: Sachs, Israel to Z, undated (Reel 365)
    - Relative Search Cards by Name A-G (Box 566)
    - Relative Search Cards by Name G-M (Box 567)
    - Relative Search Cards by Name N-S (Box 568)
    - Relative Search Cards by Name S (continued)-Z (Box 569)
    - Relative Search Microfilm Reel: A to Katz, Moses (Reel 365)
    - Relative Search Microfilm Reel: Katz, Paul (Pinchas) to Pytowski, Moishe-Mendel (Max), undated (Reel 366)
    - Relative Search Microfilm Reel: Raab, Lola to Szynicki, undated (Reel 367)
    - Relative Search Microfilm Reel: Taal, Joseph to Zyto, Joseph, undated (Reel 368)
    - Relative Search Microfilm Reel by Country: Germany and Austria, Holland, Hungary; Emigrants from Poland to Israel, Romania, Yugoslavia, undated (Reel 369)
    - Post-War Aid to Refugees Cards Africa-Germany (including Austria) (Box 570)
    - Post-War Aid to Refugees Cards Hungary-Sweden (Box 571)
    - Relative Search by Town Cards A-R (Box 572)
    - Relative Search by Town Microfilm Reel: Abel, Lithuania to Dzikow-Stary n/Jaroslaw, Galicyja (Reel 369)
    - Relative Search by Town Microfilm Reel: Eieogoloe (?), Lithuania to Rzeszow, undated (Reel 370)
  - Subseries IV:F: Jewish Labor Committee Financial Ledgers
    (Originals stored in JLC Boxes Add.23-25; see staff for access.)
    - Income and Expenses, 1934-1939 (Box Add 23)
      General
      Microfilm reel#: 371
    - General Ledger, 1937-1939 (Box Add 23)
    - Expenses, 1939-1940 (Box Add 23)
    - Income and Expenses, 1939-1940 (Box Add 23)
    - Expenses, 1939-1940, ca.1940-1942 (Box Add 23)
    - Expenses, 1940-1942 (Box Add 23)
      Microfilm reel#: 372
    - Expenses, 1943 (Box Add 24)
    - Veterans' Fund, 1943 (Box Add 24)
    - Expenses, 1944 (Box Add 24)
    - Expenses, 1942-1944 (Box Add 25)
    - Expenses, 1945-1946 (Box Add 25)
    - Expenses, 1947-1949 (Box Add 25)
      Microfilm reel#: 373